# Israel Akinpelu

UX Designer | Motion Designer | Graphics Designer

Adaptable recent graduate with a Bachelor of Science (B.Sc) in Computer Science and Engineering, with 3.5+ years of work experience. Seeking to leverage solid skills in collaboration, communication, and development as a Designer in an Organization.

### **Experience**

April 2020 - present

### Freelance Motion and UX Designer

- Maximized Advertising for CLOUDMALL AFRICA by creating promotional ads for publication.
- Translated Ideas into Products (including Web, Mobile and Video promotions.
- Created usable mobile and web designs based on functionality and aesthetically pleasing, thus meeting the customer needs.

Sept 2019 -April 2020

### Service Desk and Support Intern

**IPNX Nigeria Limited** 

- Maintained records of daily communication transactions, problems and remedial actions taken.
- Installed and performed minor repairs to hardware, software, or peripheral equipment, following design or installation specifications.
- Documented help desk requests and resolutions to provide team with fast resolutions to recurring issues, thus increasing problem resolution rate by 35%.

Aug. 2015 -Aug. 2016

# **Installation and Support Department Intern**

Tizeti Networks Ltd (wifi.com.ng)

- Diagnosed and resolve hardware, software, or other network and system problems, and replace defective components when necessary.
- Created or updated technical documentation for network installations or changes to existing installations.
- Troubleshoot network or connectivity problems for users or user groups.

### **Education**

Aug 2021 -Dec. 2021 Game Design and Development

Maliyo Gameup Africa

Aug 2016 -Dec. 2021 B.Sc (Computer Science and Engineering)

Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-ife, Osun State.

Sept 2013 -Aug. 2015 National Diploma (Computer Engineering)

First Class Honors (Upper Division) Moshood Abiola Polytechnic, Abeokuta, Ogun State.

#### Certifications

Oct 2019

Google IT supportCoursera

Jun 2020

• Google UX design Coursera

#### **Personal Info**

#### **Phone**

0809-742-2446

#### E-mail

kehneey@gmail.com

#### Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/israelkehinde

#### **Portfolio**

kabiyesi.netlify.app

#### **Soft Skills**

- · Problem Solving
- Leadership
- Ability to work in a team
- Communication skill (written)
- Communication skill (verbal)
- Flexibility/Adaptability
- Creativity
- · Strong work ethic

#### **Hard Skills**

- · UIUX Design
- Graphics Design
- Motion Design
- Desktop Support
- Remote Support
- LAN Support

# **Software Proficiency**

- Figma
- · Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After Effects
- · Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Indesign
- · Ms Office Packages
- TeamViewer
- AnyDesk
- · JIRA service desk

## Languages

- English (Native/Fluent)
- Yoruba (elementary proficient)